At last! Their epic story invades the Big Screen!
Dad's Army is a comedy, war film directed by Norman Cohen.
Dad's Army was a 1971 feature film based on the
BBC television sitcom Dad's Army.
Directed by Norman Cohen, it was filmed between series three and four and was
based upon material from the early episodes of the television series.
The film told the story of the Home Guard platoon's formation and
their subsequent endeavours at a training exercise.
Captain George Mainwaring, played by Arthur Lowe.
Sergeant Arthur Wilson, played by John Le Mesurier.
Lance Corporal Jack Jones, played by Clive Dunn.
Private James Frazer, played by John Laurie.
Private Joe Walker, played by James Beck.
Private Charles Godfrey, played by Arnold Ridley.
Dad's Army is a 1971 British war comedy film directed by Norman Cohen and starring Arthur Lowe, John
Le Mesurier, Clive Dunn, John Laurie, Arnold Ridley, Ian Lavender and James Beck.
It was written by Jimmy Perry and David Croft and was the first film
adaptation of the BBC television sitcom Dad's Army (1968–1977).
It was filmed between series three and four and was based upon
material from the early episodes of the television series.
The film tells the story of the Home Guard platoon's formation and
their subsequent endeavours at a training exercise.
The film explores themes of world war ii, home
front, seaside town, 1940s, home guard.
The tone is lighthearted.